bluecorona.com 2015-12-18

# Blue Corona Privacy Policy | Blue Corona™

This statement provides Blue Corona’s privacy policy on information that is collected through this web site and the use of that information. In General, Blue Corona may use the information it collects for management and promotion of Blue Corona. We will not sell or disclose your information for any other purpose without your written consent, unless there is a legal requirement for such disclosure. To the extent that Blue Corona discloses information to third-party contractors, those third parties will be required to follow this privacy policy.

**Information Collected During Your Visit To This Web Site**

Blue Corona is the sole owner of the information collected on this site, [www.bluecorona.com](http://www.bluecorona.com/ "www.bluecorona.com"). Blue Corona collects information from its customers at several different points on our web site. By using our services and accessing our site, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this statement, as modified from time to time by us. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post a new statement on our site and change the date indicated at the bottom of the statement. Therefore, we encourage you to check the date of our privacy policy statement whenever you visit this site for any updates or changes.

Blue Corona utilizes Google Analytics to track website visitor activity. Blue Corona has enabled Google Analytics features such as: including features such as display advertising, remarketing, and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest reporting. Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads). Users may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Personal Information**

We collect several different types of information on our site. We collect “personal information,” which is information that can be used to identify you individually, such as your name, address and telephone number. Blue Corona employees may have access to your personal information only for legitimate business purposes, and are required to protect the confidentiality of your personal information.

**Technical Information**

We automatically collect and store “technical information” about your visit to our site such as: (1) the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet; (2) the type of browser software and operating system used to access our site; (3) the date and time you access our site; and (4) the pages you visit on our site. The technical information collected will not personally identify you.

The following information explains in more detail the different forms of personal and technical information and how we may collect and use that information.

**Order Forms**

We collect personal information in connection with the purchase of items sold from this site. We request information from the customer on order forms for all products sold. A customer must provide contact information (such as name, e-mail, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number and expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill orders. If we have trouble processing an order, the information may be used to contact the customer.

**E-mail Address**

If you send us an e-mail with questions or comments or if you provide your e-mail address when ordering Blue Corona content and/or merchandise, Blue Corona may use your e-mail address and other personal information included in your correspondence to improve the content of our web site or to respond to your correspondence.

**Children’s Privacy**

Blue Corona does not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from children through Blue Corona online order forms. If at any time Blue Corona learns that a child under the age of 13 has submitted personal information online, it will take all reasonable measures necessary to remove such information from its databases and not use such information for any purpose except where necessary to protect the safety of the child or others or as required by law.

**How We Use the Information We Collect**

Blue Corona uses the information we collect from all of our web pages to provide, maintain, protect and improve the content on our sites as well as the services we offer. Blue Corona also uses this information to offer you tailored content. When you contact Blue Corona, we may keep a record of your communication to help solve any issues you might be facing. Blue Corona may use your email address to inform you about our services, such as letting you know about upcoming changes or improvements. Blue Corona uses information collected from cookies and other technologies, like pixel tags, to improve your user experience and the overall quality of our services. For example, by saving your language preferences, we’ll be able to have our services appear in the language you prefer.

When showing you tailored content, we will not associate a cookie or anonymous identifier with sensitive categories, such as those based on race, religion, sexual orientation or health. We will not combine DoubleClick cookie information with personally identifiable information unless we have your opt-in consent.

A “cookie” is a small text file that a web site can place on your computer’s hard drive in order, for example, to collect technical information about your activities on the site or to make it possible for you to use an online “shopping cart” to keep track of items you wish to purchase. The “cookie” transmits this information back to the web site’s computer that, generally speaking, is the only computer that can read it. You may set your web browser to warn you whenever a site attempts to place a cookie on your computer or refuse to accept cookies. Blue Corona will use cookies collected during your visit to this site for the purpose of facilitating your use of our site and for maintaining statistics concerning use of our site that will help us make improvements. Technical information collected by cookies will not be linked to your personal information.

Third party vendors, including Google, may show Blue Corona ads on various sites on the internet. Third party vendors, including Google, use first-party and third-party cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to Blue Corona’s website. Users may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Notification of Changes**

Blue Corona reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy and will display any changes to this privacy policy to this web site 30 days before the changes become effective. If we decide to change this privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy policy statement, the homepage, and other pages we deem appropriate so our customers are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

**How to Contact Us?**

If you have any questions about our privacy policy statement or our use of your information you can [contact us ](http://www.bluecorona.com/contact-us)directly.

**Special Notice**

Effective Date of Privacy Policy: October 1, 2013. Use of this site signifies your acceptance of Blue Corona Web Site Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy.
